{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Mobile-mas! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. When getting a new mobile device you find that it has many new settings and features. What should you do with these settings? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21927","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21931","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your device. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21927_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your device.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: D  New features are added to mobile devices all the time. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make such you understand what the main settings mean, even if you aren’t delving into advanced configuration menus.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  New features are added to mobile devices all the time. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make such you understand what the main settings mean, even if you aren’t delving into advanced configuration menus.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si21931","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. When getting a new mobile device you find that it has many new settings and features. What should you do with these settings?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_188","roles":{}},{"id":"si16169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","roles":{}},{"id":"si16077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"2. If I leave my device unattended in a public place, it’ll still be safe if I have a locking screen? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","roles":{}},{"id":"si16187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19733","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Putting on a locking screen is a great way to stop people from quickly accessing your device. If your device is stolen, however, then it is possible for cybercriminals to take the time to by-pass a locking screen. Don’t leave your mobile device unattended in public.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Putting on a locking screen is a great way to stop people from quickly accessing your device. If your device is stolen, however, then it is possible for cybercriminals to take the time to by-pass a locking screen. Don’t leave your mobile device unattended in public.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16211","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_188","si16077","si16092","si16103","si16187","si16201","si19375","si19389","si19705","si19718","si19733","si19746","si19761","si19774","si19789","si19802","si16157"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16211"},"question":{"interactionId":"16057","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. If I leave my device unattended in a public place, it’ll still be safe if I have a locking screen?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_177","roles":{}},{"id":"si16375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","roles":{}},{"id":"si16272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"3.  When using your device, what is the safest connection to send and receive sensitive information? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"A WiFi Hot-Spot ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"329","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A WiFi Hot-Spot\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"The 4G Mobile Network ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16294_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"331","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The 4G Mobile Network\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A trusted WPA2 encrypted WiFi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21319_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A trusted WPA2 encrypted WiFi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si21334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Nothing is safe ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nothing is safe\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","roles":{}},{"id":"si16393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19858","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"Correct -Answer: C  While the 4G network is a little bit more secure than public WiFi, it is still vulnerable to snooping and attacks. The safest option is always a trusted and encrypted WiFi network that is secured with WPA2.  Don’t send sensitive information over a network where it can be snooped in on.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"Incorrect - Answer: C  TWhile the 4G network is a little bit more secure than public WiFi, it is still vulnerable to snooping and attacks. The safest option is always a trusted and encrypted WiFi network that is secured with WPA2.  Don’t send sensitive information over a network where it can be snooped in on.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16417","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_177","si16272","si16287","si16298","si21323","si21338","si16393","si16407","si19403","si19417","si19817","si19830","si19845","si19858","si19873","si19886","si19901","si19914","si16363"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16417"},"question":{"interactionId":"16252","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  When using your device, what is the safest connection to send and receive sensitive information?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_178","roles":{}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","roles":{}},{"id":"si16455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"4. Consider this scenario, you are travelling over the holidays and you are bringing your personal mobile device to takes pictures of everything. What do you need to do to prepare? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"Back-up all data from the device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Back-up all data from the device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"Remove all data from the device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Remove all data from the device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Buy a temporary device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17449","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si17445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Buy a temporary device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21946","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Call the embassy ahead of time to discuss security ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21946","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21942_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Call the embassy ahead of time to discuss security\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Set-up a locking screen on your device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21961","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Set-up a locking screen on your device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Log-out of all sites. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21976","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16578q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Log-out of all sites.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","roles":{}},{"id":"si16554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"Correct -Answer: A,B,E,F  Different countries have different laws and security concerns than your home country. In some places it is legal for officials to copy the data from your phone. If you lose your phone, all that information could be in the hands of a stranger. Before travelling, make sure to back-up and remove all sensitive information, set up a locking screen, and log-out of all sites. There is no guarantee of mobile security when travelling.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A,B,E,F  Different countries have different laws and security concerns than your home country. In some places it is legal for officials to copy the data from your phone. If you lose your phone, all that information could be in the hands of a stranger. Before travelling, make sure to back-up and remove all sensitive information, set up a locking screen, and log-out of all sites. There is no guarantee of mobile security when travelling.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_178","si16455","si16470","si16481","si17449","si21946","si21961","si21976","si16554","si16568","si19431","si19445","si19929","si19942","si19957","si19970","si19985","si19998","si20013","si20026","si16524"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"},"question":{"interactionId":"16435","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. Consider this scenario, you are travelling over the holidays and you are bringing your personal mobile device to takes pictures of everything. What do you need to do to prepare?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","E","F"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_179","roles":{}},{"id":"si16697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","roles":{}},{"id":"si16616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"5. New and exciting apps are released all the time for utilities, education or games. What will help you stay secure when using mobile apps? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"Look into the apps and the publisher ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"343","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Look into the apps and the publisher\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"Deny permission requests from apps that don’t make sense ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"345","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Deny permission requests from apps that don’t make sense\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Delete the apps when you are done with them ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Delete the apps when you are done with them\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21368_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","roles":{}},{"id":"si16715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Every app on your phone is another possible target to breach your security. Make sure to review and only download apps from trusted publishers. Don’t give apps any permission that they shouldn’t have. A newsreader app should not have access to your contacts, microphone and gps location. Finally, make sure to delete apps when you are done with them to reduce any possible vulnerability.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Every app on your phone is another possible target to breach your security. Make sure to review and only download apps from trusted publishers. Don’t give apps any permission that they shouldn’t have. A newsreader app should not have access to your contacts, microphone and gps location. Finally, make sure to delete apps when you are done with them to reduce any possible vulnerability.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_179","si16616","si16631","si16642","si21357","si21372","si16715","si16729","si19459","si19473","si20041","si20054","si20069","si20082","si20097","si20110","si20125","si20138","si16685"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16739"},"question":{"interactionId":"16596","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. New and exciting apps are released all the time for utilities, education or games. What will help you stay secure when using mobile apps?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_180","roles":{}},{"id":"si16858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","roles":{}},{"id":"si16777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"6.  These days it feels like smartphones are everywhere. As of 2017, what percentage of Canadians adults use Smartphones? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"46% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"46%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_619","title":"59% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16799_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"59%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"71%  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22005_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"71%\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22020","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22024","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"92% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22020_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"92%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","roles":{}},{"id":"si16876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  According to the Pew Research Center, 71% of Canadians adults are using smartphones. That means that mobile devices are almost everywhere.  As mobile devices become more and more adopted by society, we need to understand how to work safely with them.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21382","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  According to the Pew Research Center, 71% of Canadians adults are using smartphones. That means that mobile devices are almost everywhere.  As mobile devices become more and more adopted by society, we need to understand how to work safely with them.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_180","si16777","si16792","si16803","si22009","si22024","si16876","si16890","si19487","si19501","si20153","si20166","si20181","si20194","si20209","si20222","si20237","si20250","si16846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16900"},"question":{"interactionId":"16757","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  These days it feels like smartphones are everywhere. As of 2017, what percentage of Canadians adults use Smartphones?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_181","roles":{}},{"id":"si17049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","roles":{}},{"id":"si16957","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"7.  When not using Bluetooth services, is it safe to leave Bluetooth enabled on your device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_626","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_627","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","roles":{}},{"id":"si17067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20265","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20306","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Bluetooth is best when it is enabled as little as possible. If Bluetooth is left active all the time, it leaves your device open to attacks that can target the Bluetooth receiver and compromise your information.     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Bluetooth is best when it is enabled as little as possible. If Bluetooth is left active all the time, it leaves your device open to attacks that can target the Bluetooth receiver and compromise your information.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_181","si16957","si16972","si16983","si17067","si17081","si19515","si19529","si20265","si20278","si20293","si20306","si20321","si20334","si20349","si20362","si17037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17091"},"question":{"interactionId":"16937","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  When not using Bluetooth services, is it safe to leave Bluetooth enabled on your device\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_182","roles":{}},{"id":"si17225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","roles":{}},{"id":"si17133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"8. Social Media Apps like Facebook, Snapchat, and Instagram are designed with what principle in mind? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"Protect privacy before anything else ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Protect privacy before anything else\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"Check with the user for each consideration ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check with the user for each consideration\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Collect, share and sell as much information as possible ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21580_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Collect, share and sell as much information as possible\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si21595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Profit from direct online purchases ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21595_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Profit from direct online purchases\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","roles":{}},{"id":"si17243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20390","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20405","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20433","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20446","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"Correct - Answer: C  Social media platforms thrive on that sharing and collection of information. Even with privacy and security features, the priority for most platforms is to collect your information because that is what they use for profits. Social media apps are no exception to this pattern. Often they will ask for permissions in order to gather your information to sell or use with targeted marketing. Make sure to limit the kinds of information that you share with social media.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"Incorrect - Answer: C  Social media platforms thrive on that sharing and collection of information. Even with privacy and security features, the priority for most platforms is to collect your information because that is what they use for profits. Social media apps are no exception to this pattern. Often they will ask for permissions in order to gather your information to sell or use with targeted marketing. Make sure to limit the kinds of information that you share with social media.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17267","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_182","si17133","si17148","si17159","si21584","si21599","si17243","si17257","si19543","si19557","si20377","si20390","si20405","si20418","si20433","si20446","si20461","si20474","si17213"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17267"},"question":{"interactionId":"17113","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. Social Media Apps like Facebook, Snapchat, and Instagram are designed with what principle in mind?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"dec2018Quiz2","class":"project","title":"dec2018Quiz2","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide16211","Slide16417","Slide16578","Slide16739","Slide16900","Slide17091","Slide17267","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide16211q1","Slide16417q2","Slide16578q3","Slide16739q4","Slide16900q5","Slide17091q6","Slide17267q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16211","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16417","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16739","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17091","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17267","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}